<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
    android:background="@color/white"
    android:gravity="center"
    android:orientation="vertical">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/tv_title"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="标题头" />

    <!--<LinearLayout-->
    <!--android:layout_width="match_parent"-->
    <!--android:layout_height="0dp"-->
    <!--android:layout_weight="1">-->

    <!--<ScrollView-->
    <!--android:layout_width="match_parent"-->
    <!--android:layout_height="wrap_content"-->
    android:overScrollMode="ifContentScrolls">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/tv_content"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_weight="1"
        android:scrollbars="vertical"
        android:text="内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容内容" />
    <!--</ScrollView>-->
    <!--</LinearLayout>-->

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/tv_ok"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:padding="20dp"
        android:text="知道了" />
</LinearLayout>